Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES V. Affiliates, 1930-80 (Part 2)
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES V. AFFILIATES (PART 2)
  - New York State
    - West Nyack
      - Affiliation, Correspondence from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 168, Folder 33)
        - 1976-1979 (Box 168)
      - PP of Rockland County, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1979 (Box 168, Folder 34)
      - PP of Rockland County, Trip Report, Andy Diaz, 1977 (Box 168, Folder 35)
      - PP of Rockland County from 1968
        - 1968-1974 (Box 168, Folder 36)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 168)
      - PP of Rockland County, Reports, General, 1970 (Box 168, Folder 37)
      - PP of Rockland County, Reports, Members, 1970-1971 (Box 168, Folder 38)
    - White Plains
      - PP of Westchester, Inc., Merger, 1971 (empty) (Box 168, Folder 39)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1971
        - 1972-1974 (Box 168, Folder 40)
        - 1977-1980 (Box 168)
      - Affiliation, PP of Westchester from 1971
        - 1971-1974 (Box 168, Folder 41)
        - 1977-1980 (Box 168)
      - PP of Westchester from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 168, Folder 42)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 168)
      - Affiliation, PP, General, 1953-1956 (Box 168, Folder 43)
      - PP, 1953-1954 (Box 168, Folder 44)
      - PP of Westchester, Reports, Members, 1970-1971 (Box 168, Folder 45)
    - Yonkers
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1953-1969 (Box 168, Folder 46)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence, 1962-1970 (Box 168, Folder 47)
      - PP, 1964-1969 (Box 168, Folder 48)
      - Field Trips, 1959-1964 (Box 168, Folder 49)
      - PP, Reports, Clinics, 1959-1965 (Box 168, Folder 50)
      - PP, Reports, General, 1960?-1966 (Box 168, Folder 51)
      - PP, Reports, Members, 1959-1970? (Box 168, Folder 52)
      - PP of Westchester, Public Affairs, 1977 (Box 168, Folder 53)
      - PP, Publicity, 1960-1968 (Box 168, Folder 54)
    - Northeast Region, Reports, Field Trips, 1966-1968 (Box 168, Folder 55)
    - New York City, Guttmacher, Welfare Department, 1962-1964 (Box 168, Folder 56)
    - New York City
      - Guttmacher, Hospital Department, 1962-1967 (Box 168, Folder 57)
      - Guttmacher, Health Department, 1964-1969 (Box 168, Folder 58)
    - Welfare Department, 1963-1966 (Box 168, Folder 59)
    - League for Planned Parenthood, Handbook, 1950 (Box 168, Folder 60)
    - Anti-Poverty, 1965-1971 (Box 168, Folder 61)
    - Contacts from 1964
      - 1964-1974 (Box 168, Folder 62)
      - 1975-1978 (Box 168)
    - Department of Labor, 1972 (Box 168, Folder 63)
    - Department HEW, Region 11, Family Planning Services, 1974 (Box 168, Folder 64)
    - Fair, Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 168, Folder 65)
    - Family Planning Advocates of New York State, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978-1979 (Box 168, Folder 66)
    - Family Planning Advocates of New York, 1977-1978 (Box 168, Folder 67)
    - Family Planning Information Office, 1975 (Box 168, Folder 68)
    - Genesee Region, Family Planning Program from 1971
      - 1971-1972 (Box 168, Folder 69)
      - 1976-1979 (Box 168)
    - Health Planning Advisory Council, Correspondence, 1969 (Box 168, Folder 70)
  - New York State
    - Hospitals
      - General, Correspondence, 1964-1969 (Box 168, Folder 71)
      - The Poughkeepsie Incident (Catholic), 1948-1952 (Box 168, Folder 72)
      - St. Charles Hospital Situation, 1954-1959 (Box 169, Folder 1)
      - St. Clare's Hospital Situation (Catholic), 1948-1954 (Box 169, Folder 2)
      - St. Peter's Hospital Situation (Catholic), 1959-1960 (Box 169, Folder 3)
      - The Schenectady Problem, 1958-1959 (Box 169, Folder 4)
      - Niagara Situation (Mt. St. Mary's Hospital) (Catholic), 1946-1960 (Box 169, Folder 5)
      - Strong Memorial Hospital, 1953-1961 (Box 169, Folder 6)
      - Westchester Hospital Suit, 1970 (Box 169, Folder 7)
    - Legal
      - General, Correspondence, 1964-1972 (Box 169, Folder 8)
      - Incorporation, PP Centers, 1956-1968 (Box 169, Folder 9)
      - PP Centers, Birth Control Situation, 1917-1962 (Box 169, Folder 10)
      - Misc. Material, Announcements from 1956
        - 1956-1972 (Box 169, Folder 11)
        - 1976-1978 (Box 169)
    - Medical Societies, Correspondence, 1963-1967 (Box 169, Folder 12)
    - Migrant, 1964-1972 (Box 169, Folder 13)
    - NY Penn (A 5-County Health Planning Council), 1971 (Box 169, Folder 14)
    - New York State Coalition for Family Planning
      - 1972 (Box 169, Folder 15)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 169)
    - Projects, 1969-1970 (Box 169, Folder 16)
    - Public Health, Correspondence from 1964
      - 1964-1974 (Box 169, Folder 17)
      - 1975-1978 (Box 169)
    - Public Health, Amendments to the State Hospital Code, 1976 (Box 169, Folder 18)
    - New York State Abortion Education Program, 1972-1973 (Box 169, Folder 19)
    - Public Health, Public Health Legislation in New York State, 1969 (Box 169, Folder 20)
    - Public Health, Correspondence, 1965-1970 (Box 169, Folder 21)
    - Public Welfare, Correspondence, 1964 (Box 169, Folder 22)
    - Public Welfare, Correspondence, 1963 (Box 169, Folder 23)
    - Welfare, Public (Hearings), Correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 169, Folder 24)
    - Welfare, Public (Hearings), Statements, News Clips, 1960-1966 (Box 169, Folder 25)
    - Sales Tax Exemption
      - 1965 (Box 169, Folder 26)
      - 1977 (Box 169)
    - United Fund, United Community Services, 1967-1969 (Box 169, Folder 27)
    - Wayne County, Comprehensive Community Health Center, 1970 (Box 169, Folder 28)
    - Schools, General, 1962-1974 (Box 169, Folder 29)
    - Academy of Medicine, 1962-1966 (Box 169, Folder 30)
    - Academy of Medicine, Printed Matter, Miscellaneous, 1946-1967 (Box 169, Folder 31)
    - Adelphi University, 1965-1969 (Box 169, Folder 32)
    - Columbia University
      - Correspondence, 1963-1969 (Box 169, Folder 33)
      - Bureau of Applied Social Research, 1964-1965 (Box 169, Folder 34)
      - College of Physicians & Surgeons, 1963-1969 (Box 169, Folder 35)
      - Teachers College, 1963-1972 (Box 169, Folder 36)
      - School for Social Work, 1962-1967 (Box 169, Folder 37)
      - School of Public Health, 1964-1970 (Box 169, Folder 38)
    - Cornell University, Correspondence, 1965-1970 (Box 169, Folder 39)
    - Hunter College, 1965-1969 (Box 169, Folder 40)
    - New York University, Correspondence from 1964 1964-1972 (Box 169, Folder 41)
    - University of New York, Correspondence, 1964-1974 (Box 169, Folder 42)
    - Syracuse University, 1965-1973 (Box 170, Folder 1)
    - University of Rochester, Correspondence, 1964-1972 (Box 170, Folder 2)
    - Poughkeepsie, Vassar College, 1963-1966 (Box 170, Folder 3)
    - Vassar College, Script, "Standing Room Only," Received as is, 1960 (Box 170, Folder 4)
  - North Carolina
    - Anti-Poverty, 1966-1970 (Box 170, Folder 5)
    - Family Planning Workshop, Community Action Program, 5/19/1970 (Box 170, Folder 6)
    - Contacts from 1963
      - 1963-1974 (Box 170, Folder 7)
      - 1975-1978 (Box 170)
    - Hospitals, General, Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 170, Folder 8)
    - Legal, 1947-1969 (Box 170, Folder 9)
    - Migrant, 1962-1965 (Box 170, Folder 10)
    - Projects, 1969-1971 (Box 170, Folder 11)
    - Public Health from 1964
      - 1964-1970 (Box 170, Folder 12)
      - 1975 (Box 170)
    - Public Health, Family Planning Institute, 12/16-17/63, 1963-1964 (Box 170, Folder 13)
    - Public Welfare, Correspondence, 1964-1969 (Box 170, Folder 14)
    - Public Health, Reports, Field Trips, 1957-1969 (Box 170, Folder 15)
    - Public Welfare, News, Literature, 1960-1968 (Box 170, Folder 16)
    - Solicitation, Licensing Branch, Division of Facility Services, 1977 (Box 170, Folder 17)
    - Schools, General, Correspondence, 1963-1973 (Box 170, Folder 18)
  - North Carolina
    - Chapel Hill, University of North Carolina
      - North Carolina Workshop on Problem Pregnancy, Counseling, 9/29-30/1972 (Box 170, Folder 19)
      - 1969-1974 (Box 170, Folder 20)
      - 1964-1968 (Box 170, Folder 21)
      - Conception Control Conference, 5/25/1963 (Box 170, Folder 22)
    - Durham, Duke University
      - 1962-1968 (Box 170, Folder 23)
      - Seminar, 1961-1966 (Box 170, Folder 24)
    - Durham, North Carolina College, Workshop, 1958 (Box 170, Folder 25)
    - Winston-Salem, Wake Forest College, Bowman Gray School of Medicine, 1961-1969 (Box 170, Folder 26)
    - Asheville
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, Documents, 1978 (Box 170, Folder 27)
      - Affiliation, PP of Asheville-Buncombe County, Correspondence, 1978 (Box 170, Folder 28)
      - PP of Asheville-Buncombe County, 1978 (Box 170, Folder 29)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1968-1974 (Box 170, Folder 30)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1968
        - 1968-1974 (Box 170, Folder 31)
        - 1975 (Box 170)
      - PP Western North Carolina, 1965-1974 (Box 170, Folder 32)
      - Reports, General, 1969 (Box 170, Folder 33)
      - Reports, Members, 1969-1972 (Box 170, Folder 34)
    - Chapel Hill, PP, 1966-1967 (Box 170, Folder 35)
    - Charlotte
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1970
        - 1970-1973 (Box 170, Folder 36)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 170)
      - Affiliation, PP Greater Charlotte, Correspondence from 1970
        - 1970-1974, 1980 (Box 170, Folder 37)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 170)
      - PP of Greater Charlotte, Legal, 1978 (Box 170, Folder 38)
      - PP of Greater Charlotte Community, 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 170, Folder 39)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 170)
      - Publicity, 1976 (Box 170, Folder 40)
    - Durham
      - Affiliation, Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 170, Folder 41)
      - PP of the Triangle Area, 1977-1978 (Box 170, Folder 42)
    - Raleigh, PP Assn. of Wake County from 1966
      - 1967-1968 (Box 170, Folder 43)
      - 1980 (Box 170)
    - Winston-Salem
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, Documents, 1978-1980 (Box 170, Folder 44)
      - PP of Greater Winston-Salem, 1978-1979 (Box 170, Folder 45)
      - Affiliation, PP of Greater Winston-Salem, Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 170, Folder 46)
  - North Dakota
    - Contacts from 1963
      - 1963-1972 (Box 170, Folder 47)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 170)
    - Consultation Visits: Grand Forks, Midwest Region, Ralph D.L. Price, Director, 1971 (Box 170, Folder 48)
    - Consultation Visits, Jamestown, Ralph D.L. Price, Midwest Region Director, 1971 (Box 170, Folder 49)
    - Consultation Visits: Williston, Ralph D.L. Price, 7/20-22/1971 (Box 170, Folder 50)
    - Migrants, 1968 (Box 170, Folder 51)
    - Public Health, 1961-1971 (Box 170, Folder 52)
    - Public Welfare, 1966-1972 (Box 170, Folder 53)
    - Statewide Family Planning Program & Workshops, 1970-1971 (Box 170, Folder 54)
    - Schools, General from 1970 (empty) (Box 170, Folder 55)
    - Bismarck
      - PP Committee, 1961-1964 (Box 170, Folder 56)
      - Field, 1960-1961 (Box 170, Folder 57)
      - PP Committee, Publicity, Pamphlets, etc., 1961 (Box 170, Folder 58)
    - Fargo
      - Affiliation, PP Committee, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1962-1965 (Box 170, Folder 59)
      - Affiliation, PP Committee, Correspondence, 1962-1965 (Box 170, Folder 60)
      - PP Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 170, Folder 61)
      - Field Trips, 1960-1964 (Box 170, Folder 62)
      - PP Committee, Reports, Members, 1962-1964 (Box 170, Folder 63)
      - PP Committee, Publicity, Pamphlets, etc., 1961 (Box 170, Folder 64)
    - Midwest Region, Reports, Field Trips, 1971 (Box 170, Folder 65)
  - Ohio
    - Anti-Poverty, 1965-1969 (Box 170, Folder 66)
    - Contacts, 1969-1974 (Box 170, Folder 67)
    - Contacts, 1962-1968 (Box 170, Folder 68)
    - Family Planning Conference, Columbus, Ohio 4/25-26/1971 (Box 170, Folder 69)
    - Family Planning of Southeast Ohio (Arc-Funded Project, 7 Rural Counties), 1972 (Box 170, Folder 70)
    - Hospitals, 1964-1969 (Box 170, Folder 71)
    - Legal
      - 1954-1969 (Box 170, Folder 72)
      - 1979 (Box 170)
    - Legal, Birth Control Situation, 1959-1960 (Box 170, Folder 73)
    - Migrant, 1959-1968 (Box 170, Folder 74)
    - Ohio Family Planning Council, 1972 (Box 170, Folder 75)
    - Projects, 1969 (Box 170, Folder 76)
    - Public Health, 1962-1973 (Box 170, Folder 77)
    - Public Health, Cleveland Health Museum, 1961-1963 (Box 170, Folder 78)
    - Public Welfare, 1962-1972 (Box 170, Folder 79)
    - Tax Situation, Legal, 1959 (Box 170, Folder 80)
    - United Fund, 1968-1972 (Box 170, Folder 81)
    - Schools, General, 1961-1972 (Box 170, Folder 82)
    - Medical Schools, Ohio State University and College of Medicine, 1962-1969 (Box 170, Folder 83)
    - PP Affiliates of Ohio, Inc. from 1974
      - 1974 (Box 170, Folder 84)
      - 1975-1977 (Box 170)
    - Akron
      - Dr. Gordon W. Perkin, Trip, 11/15/67, 1965 (Box 170, Folder 85)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1968
        - 1968 (Box 171, Folder 1)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 171)
      - Affiliation, PP Summit County, Correspondence from 1966
        - 1966-1972, 1980 (Box 171, Folder 2)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 171)
      - PP of Summit County from 1964
        - 1964-1974 (Box 171, Folder 3)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 171)
      - PP, Reports, Members from 1966
        - 1966-1971 (Box 171, Folder 4)
        - 1975, 1980? (Box 171)
    - Athens
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1973
        - 1973 (Box 171, Folder 5)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 171)
      - Affiliation, Correspondences from 1973
        - 1973-1974 (Box 171, Folder 6)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 171)
      - PP of Southeast Ohio from 1972
        - 1972-1974 (Box 171, Folder 7)
        - 1976-1978 (Box 171)
      - PP of Southeast Ohio, Reports, Members, 1975-1977 (Box 171, Folder 8)
    - Canton
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1967
        - 1967-1972 (Box 171, Folder 9)
        - 1975, 1978 (Box 171)
      - Affiliation, PP of Stark County, Correspondence from 1967
        - 1967-1973 (Box 171, Folder 10)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 171)
      - PP of Stark County, Trip Report, Andy Diaz, 1977 (Box 171, Folder 11)
      - PP from 1966
        - 1965-1974 (Box 171, Folder 12)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 171)
      - PP of Stark County, Reports, General, 1967-1969 (Box 171, Folder 13)
      - PP of Stark County, Reports, Members from 1967
        - 1967-1971 (Box 171, Folder 14)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 171)
    - Cincinnati
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1955
        - 1955-1973 (Box 171, Folder 15)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 171)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1956
        - 1956-1973 (Box 171, Folder 16)
        - 1976-1978 (Box 171)
      - PP Association of Cincinnati, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978-1979 (Box 171, Folder 17)
      - PP Association, 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 171, Folder 18)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 171)
      - PP Association from 1965
        - 1964-1969 (Box 171, Folder 19)
        - 1977 (Box 171)
      - PP Association, 1964 (Box 171, Folder 20)
      - Field Trips, 1954-1963 (Box 171, Folder 21)
      - PP Ohio, Reports, Clinics, 1963 (Box 171, Folder 22)
      - PP Ohio, Reports, General, 1962-1968 (Box 171, Folder 23)
    - Cleveland, Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1950
      - 1952-1973 (Box 171, Folder 24)
      - 1976-1980 (Box 171)
    - Cincinnati
      - PP Ohio, Reports, Members from 1962
        - 1962-1974 (Box 171, Folder 25)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 171)
      - PP Ohio, Publicity, 1963-1968 (Box 171, Folder 26)
    - Cleveland
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1950
        - 1950-1974 (Box 171, Folder 27)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 171)
      - PP of Cleveland, Inc. from 1971
        - 1971-1974 (Box 171, Folder 28)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 171)
      - Maternal Health Association, 1964-1970 (Box 171, Folder 29-31)
      - PP of Cleveland, Inc., Chapters from 1974
        - 1974 (Box 171, Folder 32)
        - 1976 (Box 171)
      - PP, Community Family Planning Project, Final Reports, 2/1972 (Box 171, Folder 33)
      - Field Trips, 1952-1968 (Box 171, Folder 34)
      - PP Ohio, Reports, Clinics, 1963-1973 (Box 171, Folder 35)
      - PP Ohio, Reports, General, 1963-1966 (Box 171, Folder 36)
      - PP Ohio, Reports, Members from 1963
        - 1963-1971 (Box 171, Folder 37)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 171)
      - PP Ohio, Publicity, 1957-1966 (Box 171, Folder 38)
    - Columbus
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1948
        - 1948-1973 (Box 171, Folder 39)
        - 1976-1980 (Box 171)
      - Affiliation, PP Association, Correspondence from 1953
        - 1953-1973 (Box 171, Folder 40)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 171)
      - PP of Central Ohio, Inc., 1975-1979 (Box 171, Folder 41)
      - PP Association, 1965-1974 (Box 171, Folder 42)
      - PP Association, 1964 (Box 171, Folder 43)
      - Field Trips, 1955-1961 (Box 171, Folder 44)
      - Regional Family Planning Conference, Columbus, Ohio, 4/26-27/1971 (Box 171, Folder 45)
      - PP Association, Reports, Clinics, 1959-1963 (Box 171, Folder 46)
      - PP Association, Reports, General, 1963-1968 (Box 171, Folder 47)
      - PP Association, Reports, Members from 1962
        - 1962-1971 (Box 171, Folder 48)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 171)
      - PP Association, Publicity, 1959-1968 (Box 171, Folder 49)
    - Dayton
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1965
        - 1964-1973 (Box 171, Folder 50)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 171)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1965
        - 1965-1973 (Box 171, Folder 51)
        - 1976-1979 (Box 171)
      - PP Association from 1965
        - 1965-1974 (Box 171, Folder 52)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 171)
      - PP Association, 1964 (Box 171, Folder 53)
      - Field Trips, 1953-1963 (Box 171, Folder 54)
      - Reports, General, 1964-1969 (Box 171, Folder 55)
      - PP, Reports, Members from 1964
        - 1964-1974 (Box 171, Folder 56)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 171)
      - Publicity, 1965 (Box 171, Folder 57)
    - Fremont, PP Sandusky County, 1964-1966 (Box 171, Folder 58)
    - Galion, PP Association of Crawford County, A Chapter of PP Manfield, 1972 (Box 171, Folder 59)
    - Hamilton
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1959
        - 1959-1973 (Box 171, Folder 60)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 171)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1960
        - 1960-1974, 1980 (Box 172, Folder 1)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 172)
      - PP Butler County from 1964
        - 1964-1974 (Box 172, Folder 2)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 172)
      - Field Trips, 1955-1963 (Box 172, Folder 3)
      - PP Butler County, Reports, Clinics, 1959-1973 (Box 172, Folder 4)
      - PP Butler County, Reports, General, 1959-1967 (Box 172, Folder 5)
      - Reports, Members from 1963
        - 1963-1972 (Box 172, Folder 6)
        - 1975 (Box 172)
    - Lorain
      - Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1969-1974 (Box 172, Folder 7)
      - Affiliation, Maternal Health Association of Lorain County, 1969-1974 (Box 172, Folder 8)
      - Merger: Lorain PP, Cleveland, 1974 (Box 172, Folder 9)
      - Maternal Health Association of Lorain County, 1969-1972 (Box 172, Folder 10)
    - Mansfield
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1968
        - 1968-1973 (Box 172, Folder 11)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 172)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1968
        - 1968-1974 (Box 172, Folder 12)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 172)
      - PP from 1966
        - 1965-1974 (Box 172, Folder 13)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 172)
      - Chapters of PP Association Mansfield Area, 1972 (Box 172, Folder 14)
      - Reports, Members from 1968
        - 1968-1970 (Box 172, Folder 15)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 172)
    - Newark
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1969
        - 1969-1974 (Box 172, Folder 16)
        - 1977-1980 (Box 172)
      - Affiliation, PP East Central Ohio, Correspondence from 1969
        - 1969-1974 (Box 172, Folder 17)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 172)
      - PP East Central Ohio from 1969
        - 1969-1974 (Box 172, Folder 18)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 172)
      - Reports, Members
        - 1970-1971 (Box 172, Folder 19)
        - 1975 (Box 172)
    - Painsville, Affiliation, 1957-1960 (Box 172, Folder 20)
    - Springfield
      - Affiliation, Budgets, Audits, Bylaws from 1956
        - 1963-1974 (Box 172, Folder 21)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 172)
      - Affiliation, Springfield PP Clinic, Correspondence from 1957
        - 1956-1972 (Box 172, Folder 22)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 172)
    - Field Trips, Painsville, 1955 (Box 172, Folder 23)
    - Springfield
      - PP Clinic, Reports, General, 1957-1963 (Box 172, Folder 24)
      - PP Clinic from 1963
        - 1963-1974 (Box 172, Folder 25)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 172)
      - PP Clinics, Publicity, 1957 (Box 172, Folder 26)
      - PP Clinic, Reports, Members, 1961-1963 (Box 172, Folder 27)
      - Field Trips, 1953-1963 (Box 172, Folder 28)
      - Dr. Calderone's Trip, 4/60, 1959-1960 (Box 172, Folder 29)
    - Toledo
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1951
        - 1951-1972 (Box 172, Folder 30)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 172)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1960
        - 1960-1974 (Box 172, Folder 31)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 172)
      - PP of Greater Toledo, Inc.
        - 1969-1974 (Box 172, Folder 32)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 172)
      - PP League, 1963-1968 (Box 172, Folder 33)
      - Field Trips, 1954-1963 (Box 172, Folder 34)
      - PP League, Reports, Clinics, 1963-1969 (Box 172, Folder 35)
      - PP League, Reports, General from 1963
        - 1963-1970 (Box 172, Folder 36)
        - 1976 (Box 172)
      - PP League, Reports, Members from 1963
        - 1964-1972 (Box 172, Folder 37)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 172)
      - PP League, Publicity, 1961-1968 (Box 172, Folder 38)
    - Warren
      - Affiliation, PP Trumbell County, Correspondence, 1969-1972 (Box 172, Folder 39)
      - PP Association of Trumbell County, 1969-1972 (Box 172, Folder 40)
    - Youngstown
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1955
        - 1955-1972 (Box 172, Folder 41)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 172)
      - Affiliation, Correspondence from 1963
        - 1955-1972 (Box 172, Folder 42)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 172)
      - PP of Mahoning Valley, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1979 (Box 172, Folder 43)
      - Merger: Warren-Youngstown, 1971-1972 (Box 172, Folder 44)
      - PP from 1963
        - 1963-1974 (Box 172, Folder 45)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 172)
      - Field Trips, 1954-1963 (Box 172, Folder 46)
      - PP Association, Reports, General, 1960-1965 (Box 172, Folder 47)
      - PP Association, Reports, Members from 1960
        - 1960-1972 (Box 172, Folder 48)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 172)
  - Oklahoma
    - Anti-Poverty Program, 1964-1968 (Box 172, Folder 49)
    - Contacts from 1965
      - 1965-1972 (Box 172, Folder 50)
      - 1976 (Box 172)
    - Hospitals from 1962
      - 1962 (Box 172, Folder 51)
      - 1977 (Box 172)
    - Legal, 1942-1969 (Box 172, Folder 52)
    - Master Plan for the State of Oklahoma, (Langmyhr, George, M.D.), 1967 (Box 172, Folder 53)
    - Migrant, 1964-1968 (Box 172, Folder 54)
    - Public Health, 1962-1972 (Box 172, Folder 55)
    - Public Welfare, 1965-1971 (Box 172, Folder 56)
    - United Fund, United Community Services, 1968-1969 (Box 172, Folder 57)
    - Schools, 1965-1968 (Box 172, Folder 58)
    - University of Oklahoma, 1963-1971 (Box 172, Folder 59)
    - Muskogee
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence, 1965-1971 (Box 172, Folder 60)
      - PP Committee, 1963-1970 (Box 172, Folder 61)
      - Reports, General, 1966-1969 (Box 172, Folder 62)
      - Reports, Members, 1965-1969 (Box 172, Folder 63)
    - Norman
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1966-1972 (Box 172, Folder 64)
      - PP Association, Correspondence, 1966-1972 (Box 172, Folder 65)
      - PP Association, Cleveland County, 1965-1971 (Box 172, Folder 66)